Hello, everyone. Welcome
back to English Pod.
My name is Marco and I'm Erica
and today we're bringing you a very
I would say embarrassing
lesson for us men right
embarrassing for men, but
I think it's okay for women
That's right. We're gonna
be talking about buying
underwear specifically
women's underwear, right?
So obviously not the
favorite thing for men to do
well apart from being a
little bit uncomfortable
It's also boring. Yeah, it
involves shopping, right?
It involves shopping. So
we're not really big on that
All right, but well even though it
might be a little bit of an uncomfortable
Topic, there is some great
language in here, isn't there?
Yeah, there's some really
good words and of course
The different types of underwear that we're
gonna be looking at. Yeah, but we also
have some words that we're
gonna take a look at before we
get into our dialogue So let's
start with vocabulary preview
Vocabulary preview. Well, we're
gonna look at two words that
will appear in our dialogue
and the first one is lingerie
lingerie lingerie
Okay, so lingerie. This is a
nice fancy word. Mm-hmm.
Basically for underwear, right?
Right for women's underwear
Women's underwear. Yeah, so lingerie,
but it's very nice very pretty sexy
Yeah, yeah, now the
spelling of this word is
interesting, isn't it?
Yeah, it's spelled L I N G
E R I E lingerie lingerie. Yes,
don't you love English spelling?
So women's nice pretty sexy underwear.
That's right. And our second word awkward
awkward awkward awkward
So this is a feeling that men
have especially when they're buying
women's underwear. Well, yeah,
you feel a little bit uncomfortable
Yeah, it's a strange situation weird
or out of place. It's awkward. Yes
Alright, so we're gonna be
hearing both of these two
words in the dialogue now
Michael. Where are we here?
We're gonna be at a department store
at the section where they have women's
lingerie and we have a guy
buying underwear for his girlfriend.
All right. Well, let's
find out what happens
This sucks, but hate buying lingerie
Okay, just find something and get
out of here. All right, these are fine.
Oh, no, don't come over
here. Don't come over here
You look a little lost. Can I help you?
Um, I'm just having a look around
It's my girlfriend's birthday tomorrow.
I'm trying to find her something
Well, you can't give
her granny panties.
Have you thought about
getting her some sleepwear?
We've got these lovely silky 90s or how
about some nice panties on the bra set?
Look, here's a nice satin
push-up bra, and you can choose
a few different styles
of undies to go with it.
Sure That's fine
This is so awkward
What wants to my
pick? What size is she?
Well, do you want to
thong some bikini briefs?
Maybe this nice pair
of lacy boy shorts.
Just pick something and
get the hell out of here
Um, I'll go with these two
This is mortifying. I
just want to get this
over with and she
better thank you for those
Here you are, sir.
I'm sure she'll enjoy them. Finally
I'm sorry, sir. I'm going to have
to take a look inside your bag
Oh the poor guy I totally feel bad for him.
Yeah, he was really nervous and of course
It was very
uncomfortable for him.
I know and then the security
guard shows up. Exactly
But we have the opportunity to take a
look at some really great words and phrases
So let's start off with their
first one in language takeaway
Language takeaway
All right, we're gonna look
out words here that mostly
have to do with underwear
describing underwear, right?
And the first one
is Granny panties
Granny panties Granny panties.
This isn't like a real real word, right?
It's not something you'll
find at the dictionary.
No, it's a slang word
and we use it to describe
Really big ugly underwear like
your grandmother would wear.
All right, so they're not like the
sexy little underwear more like long
And it's not very appealing. Just picture
what your grandmother would wear. No
All right, so granny panties so obviously
This guy doesn't want to
be buying any of those, but
the saleswoman suggests
that he try some sleepwear
Sleepwear sleepwear sleepwear.
Okay, so sleepwear
Obviously close you wear
when you're sleeping now
This is really interesting because
men aren't really that complicated
when it comes to sleeping just
throw on a t-shirt and that's it
Well, obviously for women
there are more options
and more different
things you can choose from
Okay, the whole separate
category for women even when
you're sleeping you must
wear something nice. Yes
One type of sleepwear
is silky 90s 90s 90s, and I
G H T I E S okay. So a 90 it's basically
a dress that you wear when you sleep
Okay, now the pronunciation
is interesting because the first
five letters are night. Right,
right, but you don't say night
You don't say nighty. You say nighty.
Yeah, you make the tea a D 90 now
She offered him some silky 90s, right?
So silky
Obviously, we know silk
is a soft shiny fabric, right?
So when something is silky, it's either
made from silk or it's soft and shiny.
Okay, so some silky
night is very soft shiny
90s exactly. Okay. What
about our next word?
Well, the sales girl offers
different styles of undies
undies undies undies. So
undies is an interesting word.
It's basically short for
underwear underwear. Okay
So you can just call underwear
undies. Yes, but I think you
mostly use this when you're
talking about women's underwear
Oh, really? I mean, I don't
know if I would say undies when
I'm talking about men's
underwear. No, I don't think so
Maybe children's underwear.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah for
children for children,
right? Yep. Okay.
All right So we saw some of
the different types of clothing, but
now let's take a look at
this interesting adjective
Modifying more defying.
This is mortifying more defying
Okay, so when something
is mortifying well, I think
we've got some examples
to show you what that is like
example one
And then I fell in front of everyone.
It was mortifying
Example two
I was completely mortified
when I realized what I had done
Example three
It must have been mortifying for her when
she realized that her underwear was showing
So basically it's very
embarrassing super embarrassing.
You want to die almost. Yep.
Okay, which is I interesting
I mean more right? Yeah,
right. Yeah. Yeah. Interesting.
All right. Well, um,
etymology here at English hot
All right, so some interesting
Okay, so we saw the
different types of underwear
We saw this really great word
for when you're really embarrassed
So now let's take a look at
some of the phrases that you
would use when you're really
embarrassed influence you builder
Fluency builder. All right, we have
two phrases to look at here. The first one
Get the hell out of here
Get the hell out of here.
Okay, so if I say I want
to get the hell out of here
You want to leave
this place really quickly.
Really quickly. Yes, I
want to leave right now
Now when you're using this this phrase
or this sentence get the hell out of here
Is it really polite?
No, of course not.
It's it's in polite. Okay,
so it's really negative
Very negative and informal
right. Yeah. Yeah, so you would
use this maybe with your
friends or like in this case
Think it to yourself. Yes,
but it's not a good idea
to use with your boss
or your mother. All right
Okay, I guess sometimes
depending on the tone you
use how you say it you
can sound really angry, right?
Definitely right. Okay. All right.
Well, let's listen to some examples
Example one
This place is scary.
Let's get the hell out of here
Example two
What are you doing in my
house get the hell out of here?
Example three
We're the friends party and all
of a sudden the parents arrived.
We got the hell out of
there as quickly as possible
All right, so get the hell out of
here get the hell out of here now
Let's take a look at our
last phrase for a fluency
builder get this over
with get this over with
I want to get this over with
So you want to finish it really quickly
But you want to finish it because
you're not really enjoying it, right?
Exactly This is something that you use
when the situation is negative is negative.
Okay, so I just want
to get this over with
Yeah, I want to get
this test over with I want
to get this day over
with I want to get this
Maybe if you're on a bad date. I want
to get this date over with. Yes exactly
All right, well interesting
phrases and I think it would
help us to hear them once
more in context in the dialogue
This sucks. I hate buying lingerie
Okay, just find something
and get out of here
All right, these are fine. Oh, no don't
come over here. Don't come over here
You look a little lost. Can I help you?
I'm just having a look around
It's my girlfriend's birthday tomorrow.
I'm trying to find her something
Well, you can't give
her granny panties.
Have you thought about
getting her some sleepwear?
We've got these lovely silky 90s or
how about some nice panties on a bra set?
Look, here's a nice satin
push-up bra and you can
choose a few different styles of
undies to go with it Sure, that's fine
This is so awkward Well, this
is my pick. What size is she?
Well, do you want to
thong some bikini briefs?
Maybe this nice pair
of lacy boy shorts.
Just pick something and
get the hell out of here
Um, I'll go with these two
This is mortifying. I just want to get this
over with and she better thank you for this
Here you are, sir.
I'm sure she'll enjoy them
I'm sorry, sir. I'm going to have
to take a look inside your bag
All right, so I guess the situation
is very common men either
having to shop for this type of
article for their girlfriend or wife
Because it's their birthday. Yeah, or
sometimes we get dragged into a store to
To buy this. You're shopping
with your girlfriend and
she's gonna make you go
look at underwear with her
Yeah, I usually don't do
that though. I will just go
to the next section and
just look around look at tools
TVs and play stations
Yes, but you know what I have
seen some men who go shopping with
their girlfriends or wives and
actually enjoy buying underwear
See, that's the thing.
I think it it makes sense
But I don't know how
comfortable you would actually be.
I don't know why I guess just a
how it indicates sexuality and stuff
Like I could do it for
maybe five or ten minutes
give my professional
advice and I'm out of there
All right, well, maybe those
guys who look like they're
enjoying themselves are just
really talking in their heads
Telling themselves how much
they hate this exactly maybe they're
just they're pretending
pretending or listening to their iPod
Well, tell us well guys I know we've got
a lot of male listeners tell us what you
think are you embarrassed by
women's underwear right or women?
Why aren't you embarrassed
when you buy men's
underwear for your
boyfriend or husband?
I think there's a lot to talk about here.
So come to our website at englishpod.com
Right leave your questions
and comments and of
course tell us what you
think about this topic
Well, thanks for downloading this
lesson and until next time goodbye